"""question_data = [
{"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
{"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
{"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]"""

question_data = [{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main.py directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Pluto is a planet.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
